rockandrepublic.com 2016-04-10

# Kohl's

Sponsored Links 

The links below are ads provided by the Google AdWords™ program. Outside companies pay to advertise via these links when specific phrases and words are searched. These ads are provided by Google and are labeled as sponsored links. Clicking on these links will open a new tab displaying that respective company's own website. The website you link to is not affiliated with or sponsored by Kohls.com

## (Updated as of June 5, 2014)

### SCOPE

Welcome! This Privacy Policy ("Policy") applies to customer information collected and used by Kohl's Corporation and its affiliates in Kohl's retail stores ("Stores") and on our "Site." For purposes of this privacy policy, "Site" means those websites linking to this Policy, including without limitation, Kohls.com, its related subdomains and microsites, Kohl's mobile applications, and Kohls.com accessed through Kohl's kiosks and/or your mobile device. To read our full Privacy Policy, please click here. To view your separate Kohl's Credit Card Privacy Policy, please click [here](https://credit.kohls.com/eCustService/).

_Read more about"Scope"_

### TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect your information, including certain personal information, such as your name, address, phone number, email address, location information, and more, from various sources, including:

  * Information collected when you interact with us, such as during transactions, completion of forms, registration or surveys, and through your participation in our marketing incentives and programs; 
  * Information from other sources, such as companies that help us to update our records; and
  * Information automatically collected when you visit or use our Site or view our online ads, such as via cookies and device information, and in Stores, such as through your use of our Wi-Fi Services.

_  
Read more about"Types of Information We Collect"_

### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We may use the information we collect to provide the products and services you request, to tell you about other products and services Kohl's or other companies offer, and to manage our Site and services.

All of the information we collect about you, whether through our Site or in our Stores, may be combined for marketing and promotional purposes, to improve our communications with you, to enhance the content of our Site, and to optimize your overall Kohl's shopping experience across channels.

_Read more about"How We Use Your Information"_

### HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

We may share your information with the following:

  * Companies that provide support services to us and our business partners;
  * Third parties that provide financial products and services related to our business, such as Kohl's Charge; and
  * Authorities or other third parties if required by law or based upon our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with the law, to protect users of our Site or the Site itself, to protect the public or to otherwise protect and defend the rights and property of Kohl's.

_  
Read more about"How We Share Your Information"_

### MOBILE AND LOCATION-BASED SERVICES

The following also applies, as applicable, to your use of Kohl's mobile website, mobile applications and/or Kohl's Wi–Fi Services in our Stores:

  * Kohl's collects certain information automatically, such as the type of mobile device you use; device identifier; your mobile operating system; pages you visit on our mobile site; search terms; the type of mobile Internet browsers you use; and information about the way you use our mobile website and applications.
  * If you elect to utilize the location-based features and functionalities made available by Kohl's through its mobile website or mobile applications or simply by using Kohl's Wi-Fi Services in our Stores, Kohl’s may collect precise location-based information;

_  
Read more about"Mobile and Location-Based Services"_

### CHOICES REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION

_Email_ : 

  * Use the unsubscribe link on any Kohl's promotional emails.
  * Use this link to unsubscribe from all future promotional emails: <http://www.kohls.com/homepage/sale_alert_unsub.jsp>.

_  
Text Messages & Mobile Coupons_: 

  * Follow the opt-out instructions provided in each text message or mobile coupon or contact Kohl's Customer Service toll free at (866) 887-8884.

_  
Mobile Application and Location Based Services_ : 

  * If you have previously opted into Kohl's collection and use of location-based information through our mobile application, you may opt-out by adjusting the Settings on your mobile device.
  * Additionally, you may opt-out of all location-based information collection by uninstalling the Kohl's mobile application and refraining from using Kohl's Wi–Fi Services available in some Stores. 

_  
Postal Mail_ : 

  * Send your request (including full name and mailing address) to   
Kohl’s Department Stores, Inc.  
PO Box 3120  
Milwaukee, WI 53201.
  * Call Customer Service at (866) 887-8884.

_  
Cookies & Similar Technologies_: 

  * Refer to the Help function of your browser to learn more about cookie settings and options. Refer to the Help function of your browser to learn more about cookie settings and options.

_  
Interest-Based Advertising_ : 

  * For information about opt out programs that our third-party advertising vendors may participate in, and the effect of opting out, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

_  
Omniture and Google Analytics_ : 

  * Omniture: Click the following link for more information about Omniture and your choices: <http://www.adobe.com/privacy.html>
  * Google Analytics: Click the following links for more information about Google Analytics and your choices: <http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html> and <https://www.google.com/settings/ads>

_  
Read more about"Choice Regarding Your Information"_

### HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions, comments or concerns with respect to our privacy practices or this Policy, please feel free to contact us at [customer.service@kohls.com](mailto:customer.service@kohls.com)

### SCOPE

Welcome! This privacy policy applies to customer information collected and used by Kohl's Corporation and its affiliates in Kohl's retail stores ("Stores") and on our "Site." For purposes of this privacy policy, "Site" means those websites linking to this Policy, including without limitation, Kohls.com, its related subdomains and microsites, Kohl's mobile applications and Kohls.com accessed through Kohl's kiosks and/or your mobile device. To view your separate Kohl's Credit Card Privacy Policy, please click [here](https://credit.kohls.com/eCustService/). 

Please take a moment to read our Privacy Policy ("Policy") which explains what type of information is collected both in our Stores and through our Site, how that information is used, to whom it is disclosed, and how it is safeguarded. By using the Site and shopping in our Stores, you agree to the terms of this Policy and our use of your information as described in this Policy, and you expressly agree to comply with Kohl's [Legal Notices](http://www.kohls.com/catalog/common/content.jsp?pageName=legalnotices).

Back to Top

### TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

(a) _Information Collected When You Interact with Kohl's:_  
We collect information, including personal information, from you in a variety of ways when you interact with Kohl's, both in our Stores and through our Site. Examples of information we may collect include your name, home address, email address, telephone number, mobile phone number, precise location information, mobile device identification, Site traffic and navigational information, credit card number, purchase and order information, demographical information and event-related information for gift registries. Such information can be collected, for instance, when:

  * You follow the checkout process and make an online or in-store purchase, return or exchange;
  * You purchase an electronic gift card;
  * You create a personalized Kohls.com shopping account for your convenience;
  * You use our online order tracking;
  * You sign up to receive promotional emails or text messages (including offers and sales alerts);
  * You sign up to join a loyalty, rewards or similar program or club;
  * You provide your contact information and product preferences in consulting with our beauty associates;
  * You participate in one of our promotional sweepstakes, contests and/or surveys or focus groups;
  * You create or update a gift registry;
  * You use the Ratings & Reviews or related services and features;
  * You submit a request to our Customer Service team;
  * You sign up for, and/or maintain, a [Kohl’s Charge card](https://credit.kohls.com/eCustService/);
  * You use and navigate Kohl’s Sites, including features to find store locations;
  * You click on sponsored links or third-party advertisements;
  * You install, use, and navigate Kohl’s mobile applications and/or mobile website;
  * You participate in the Kohl’s Blog and/or use Kohl’s pages on social media sites, such as Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Pinterest and Instagram ("Social Media Pages").
  * You use the Wi-Fi Services provided in some Stores.

(b) _Information from Other Sources:_  
We may receive information about you from other sources and third parties. For instance, we obtain information from companies to enhance our existing customer information, such as improving the accuracy of the information we have about our customers. 

Back to Top

### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

Examples of how we may use your information include: (i) to process purchase, return or exchange transactions; (ii) to provide the products or services you request; (iii) to improve our Site and our Stores; (iv) to market and promote purposes; (v) to communicate with you; and (vi) to enhance your overall Kohl's shopping experience across channels. In order to accomplish these objectives, we may also combine information about you that we collect in our Stores and through our Site, including, your use of our mobile applications and Wi–Fi Services 

Back to Top

### HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

(a) _Internally_ : We may share your information within Kohl’s Corporation, including with our affiliates

(b) _Merger or Acquisition_ : In the event that Kohl’s and/or its affiliates would merge with, acquire or be acquired by another business entity as well as (or portions through) an asset sale or is involved in a corporate reorganization or other change of control, some or all of the personal information collected about you could be shared, as well as retained by Kohl’s.

(c) _Service Providers_ : We provide your information to companies that provide support services to Kohl's, such as: printers, marketing providers, analytics companies, web hosting providers, contest and survey administrators, call center service providers, payment processors, fulfillment and logistics vendors and data verification providers. We may also share your personal information with third parties that provide financial products and services related to our business, such as Kohl's Charge. These companies need your personal information to perform their functions, to fulfill your requests and to make your shopping experience more satisfying.

(d) _Elsewhere at your Direction_ : At your direction, we may share your information. For instance, if you participate in any Kohl's Gift Registry, you agree that your name(s), event date(s), state and complete Gift List will be viewable on the Site, our partnership Gift Registry websites and/or in Kohl's Stores to anyone who searches, finds and selects the registrants' names when using the Gift Registry feature. If Gift Registry participants do not want this information accessible on Kohls.com and/or our partnership Gift Registry websites, they may call Kohl's Customer Service toll free at (866) 887-8884 to request registry access be restricted to Kohl's Stores only.

(e) _Legal or Safety Requirements_ : Kohl's may disclose specific information about you if necessary to do so by law or based upon our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with the law, to protect users of our Site or the Site itself, to protect the public or to otherwise protect and defend the rights and property of Kohl's. 

Back to Top

### MOBILE AND LOCATION-BASED SERVICES

The following applies to your use of Kohl’s mobile website, mobile applications, and/or Kohl’s Wi–Fi Services in our Stores:

(a) _Mobile Coupons & Text Messages_: Kohl's distributes mobile coupons and text messages to mobile devices of customers who have requested the coupons and consented to the text messages via an opt–in request. The opportunity to opt–out of a specific text message marketing campaign will be made available with the messages we send. Refer to "Choices Regarding Your Information" section below for more options. 

(b) _Information Collected Automatically_ : Kohl's collects certain information automatically, such as the type of mobile device you use; device identifier; your mobile operating system; pages you visit on our mobile site; search terms; the type of mobile Internet browsers you use; and information about the way you use our mobile website and applications.

(c) _Precise Location Information_ : If you elect to utilize the location-based features and functionalities made available by Kohl's through its mobile website or mobile applications, or simply by using Kohl's Wi–Fi Services in our Stores, Kohl's may collect mobile device identification and precise, real–time location-based information from technologies like Wi–Fi, or cell tower triangulation (or a combination of these technologies). If you do not want Kohl's to use location-based information, please refrain from using Kohl's Wi–Fi services or any location-based service offered through our mobile website or through a Kohl's mobile application or click "Don't Allow" when your mobile device requests your location-based information. Once you elect to allow location-based services through a Kohl's mobile application, you are agreeing that we can use your location data when you use location-based features like the store locator, and we can continue to collect your location information when you are at a Kohl's Store unless you turn off location-based services for the Kohl's mobile application. Refer to "Choices Regarding Your Information" section below for more options.

(d) _Other Information_ : With respect to other information collected through our mobile website or Kohl's mobile applications, we may collect the same type of information as addressed in "Types of Information We Collect" and will use and share the collected information in the manner described in "How We Use Your Information" and "How We Share Your Information."

Back to Top

### COOKIES & SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES

(a) _General_ : A cookie is a small text file sent by a website that is stored on your hard drive by your computer's browser. At Kohls.com, we use two kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies exist only for as long as your browser remains open. We use session cookies, for example, to add items to your shopping bag. Persistent cookies last from visit to visit and do not go away when you exit your browser. We use persistent cookies to give you a more personalized shopping experience and to streamline your website navigation. For example, we use persistent cookies to show you items you have previously browsed on Kohls.com. Managing cookies varies from browser to browser, so please refer to your browser for further information. If you would like to disable cookies from Kohls.com, please use the help function in your web browser to restrict cookies from our Site. If you block cookies from Kohls.com, you may not be able to make purchases or use other interactive features of our Site. 

We also use pixel tags (sometimes called "web beacons" or "clear gifs"), which are tiny graphic images, on our websites and in our emails. Pixel tags help us analyze our customers' online behavior, collecting information about your visit, including pages you view, links you click, whether you open an email or if our banner ads on our Site or other websites are effective. The information collected may include your computer's Internet protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your operating system, date and time information, and other technical information about your computer. We may also track certain information about the identity of the website you visited immediately before and immediately after coming to our Site, including banner ads bringing you to or taking you from Kohls.com

Identifiers for Advertising ("IFA") or other device identifiers may be used when you use Kohl's mobile application or utilize Kohl's Wi–Fi Services in Stores, as described in the Mobile and Location-Based Services portion of this Policy.

Kohl's may also use service providers and/or third party analytic companies acting on behalf of Kohl's to implement these cookies, pixel tags and similar technologies to help us track, collect and analyze this information to improve our Site. 

(b) Technology Used to Serve Advertisements on Websites. Kohl's and our third-party advertising vendors, such as Google, use first– and third– party cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads on our website and other websites based upon a user's past visits to our Site and other websites, and to report upon how Kohl's ad impressions and other ad services are related to the Site. We may combine and associate the information we collect through these technologies with other information we have collected from and about you. This collective information may be used by our third–party advertising vendors for interest-based advertising (also called "online behavioral advertising") on our website and other websites across the internet in order to personalize your online experience, improve our Site and other websites, and to tailor Kohl's and other companies' marketing to you. To learn more about this process or to opt-out of this type of advertising, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Back to Top

(a) _Personal Information Collected Directly by Kohl’s_ : Kohl's may collect personal information from you through our Social Media Pages if you provide it. Examples of how personal information may be collected directly on Social Media Pages include your provision of information through (i) an application or form which links to this Policy, including Kohl's sweepstakes or contests appearing on our Social Media Pages; and/or (ii) you interact with a Kohl's representative concerning a customer service or other issue, question, or comment.

(b) _Personal Information Collected by the Social Media Sites_ : This Policy does not cover the privacy and security practices of the social media sites on which Kohl's has Social Media Pages. Please review the privacy policies and terms of use on the Social Media Pages if you have any questions about their privacy or security practices.

The social media sites where Kohl's has its Social Media Pages may provide aggregate and customer information and analysis to Kohl's about visitors' use of our Social Media Pages and Kohl's advertising on these sites.

Back to Top

### CHOICES REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION

(a) _Email_ : Each promotional email you receive from Kohl's will offer you the continuing opportunity to cancel or opt-out of Kohl's email list. In addition, if you decide that you would rather not receive promotional emails from us in the future, you may unsubscribe at this address: <http://www.kohls.com/homepage/sale_alert_unsub.jsp>

(b) _Mobile Coupons & Text Messages_: If you have signed up for text messages and/or mobile coupons, but later decide you no longer wish to receive them, you can simply follow the opt–out instructions provided in each mobile message, or you can contact Kohl's Customer Service toll free at (866) 887-8884.

(c) _Mobile Application and Location-Based Services_ : If you do not want Kohl's to use location-based information, please refrain from using a location–based service or functionality or click "Don't Allow" when your mobile device requests your location-based information. In addition, if you previously opted into Kohl's collection and use of location-based information through our mobile application, you may turn off location–based services for the Kohl's mobile application at any time through the Settings on your mobile device.

Additionally, you can stop collection of all location–based information by uninstalling the application and refraining from using Kohl's Wi–Fi Services available in some Stores. You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network.

(d) 

_Postal Mail_

: If you wish to be removed from the list of customers who receive direct mail through the post mail, please contact Kohl's Customer Service toll free at (866) 887-8884 or send your request to the following address (please be sure to include your full name and mailing address where you are receiving the direct mail that you wish to discontinue): 

Kohl’s Department Stores, Inc.  
PO Box 3120  
Milwaukee, WI 53201

(e) _Cookies & Similar Technologies_: Refer to the Help function of your browser to learn more about cookie settings and options. Refer to the Help function of your browser to learn more about cookie settings and options. 

(f) _Interest-Based Advertising_ : For more information about opt-out programs that our third-party advertising vendors may participate in, and the effect of opting out, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

(h) 

_Update Your Information_

: If you have created a Kohls.com shopping account and/or a gift registry, you can update your information by signing back into your account or registry. If you have any other requests, please contact Kohl's Customer Service toll free at (866) 887-8884 or send your request to the following address: 

Kohl’s Department Stores, Inc.  
PO Box 3043  
Milwaukee, WI 53201

Back to Top

### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Under California law, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. The notice will identify the categories of personal information shared with third parties, as well as the name and address of the third parties that receive such personal information. If you want a copy of this notice, please submit a written request, specifying that you want a "Kohl's California Privacy Notice," to the following address: 

Kohl’s Department Stores, Inc.   
Attn. Kohls.com Team   
PO Box 3043   
Milwaukee, WI 53201 

**California Do Not Track Disclosure**  
California residents are also advised that Kohl's (and certain third parties authorized by Kohl's) does track users' behavior on our Site and across websites for the purpose of serving targeted ads, for instance, or as further described in the How We Use Your Information above. As noted, we use third–party advertising vendors that use first– and third– party cookies to gather information as customers interact with Kohl's Site and interact with other websites. Once gathered, this information helps Kohl's and other companies to serve ads on our website and other websites. For information about opt-out programs that our third-party advertising vendors may participate in, and the effect of opting-out, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>. You should be aware that our Site may not recognize Do Not Track header information from some or all browsers. 

Back to Top

### SECURITY

Whether you are shopping in our Stores or on our Site, we maintain physical, technical and procedural security measures to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. 

(a) _Online Security_ : Kohls.com utilizes Secure Sockets Layering ("SSL") to encrypt the information you provide (including, but not limited to, name, address and credit card number) as it is transmitted across the Internet to Kohls.com. This means you should not be able to place an order through an unsecured connection.

Although we will take reasonable security precautions regarding your personal information collected from and stored on the Site, because of the open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any of your personal information stored on our servers or on those of our third parties, or transmitted to or from Kohls.com, will be free from unauthorized access or disclosure. Accordingly, and as set forth in our [Legal Notices](http://www.kohls.com/catalog/common/content.jsp?pageName=legalnotices), we disclaim any liability for any unauthorized access to, disclosure or damage to, interception of, theft, or loss of any data communications and/or personal information. By using the Site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.

Kohl’s is also BBB Accredited for the Web. Click on the BBB Seal below to learn more about this certification.

(b) _In-store Cameras_ : Kohl's uses in-store cameras, primarily for fraud-detection and security, as well as for operational and customer insight purposes, such as measuring traffic patterns.

Back to Top

### CHILDREN UNDER 13

The Site, including its mobile applications and tools, is not marketed to, and does not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from, children under the age of 13.

Back to Top

### MY KOHL'S CHARGE

Please review the My Kohl's Charge Online Privacy Policy available on the [My Kohl’s Charge website](http://credit.kohls.com/) to learn how any information you provide to My Kohl's Charge is protected and used.

Back to Top

### LINKS

For your convenience, our Site may contain links to outside websites. Kohl's is not responsible for the web practices of those sites, and we expressly disclaim liability and responsibility for those links. Please view the respective privacy policies and terms of use provided on those sites if you have any questions about their web practices, which Kohl's has neither reviewed nor endorsed.

Back to Top

### CHANGES IN POLICY

As we continue to offer new and different types of content and services, Kohl's may modify our collection and use practices covered by this Policy. Should there be a material change to our information practices, it will be applied only to information collected on a go-forward basis, and we will update this privacy policy statement, as reflected by updating the date at the beginning of this Policy. For this reason, Kohl's encourages you to review this Policy statement each time you visit this Site.

Back to Top

### HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions, comments or concerns with respect to our privacy practices or this Policy, please feel free to contact us at [customer.service@kohls.com](mailto:customer.service@kohls.com)

Back to Top

© 2015 Kohl's Department Stores, Inc. All rights reserved.
